Here We Are is a drama film directed by William Clift.
An interracial gay couple navigates racism and bigotry in a world in turmoil.
When Phil loses his mom to conspiracies and booze, and meets John, a lawyer with it all,
they finally face their buried pasts to discover who they really are.
Phil, played by Mel England.
John, played by Wil J. Jackson.
Sherri, played by Sally Kirkland.
Karen, played by Christine Elise.
Terry, played by Gregory Zarian.
Barb, played by Elizabeth Regen.
Here We Are is a musical with music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim and a book by David Ives inspired by two
films of Luis Buñuel, The Exterminating Angel and The Discreet Charm of the Bourgeoisie.
The tone is emotional.